Guide to the Douglas C. Engelbart Papers M0638
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Accession 1998-094
  - Alphabetical Files, 1962-1991
    - Alpha Files A-M 1988
      - Gartner Group, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Grist, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Greene, Stu, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Hammond, Edward H., 1988 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Horn, Robert, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Hyper Base, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Hypertext, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Hyperfest, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Idea Futures, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Kochen Stevens, Gordon, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Lantz, Keith, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Lynch, Dan, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - MB Files, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - MM Summary, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - MDC3, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - MDC, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Malone, Thomas W, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - MM to Ontyme, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Alpha Files A-J 1989
      - Starting Bootstrap at SU, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Demo NP, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Dialog Grist, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Idea Futures, Gaming, Society, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Independent Labs, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Academic Information Resources, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - ARC, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - ATF, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Agenda/Demo, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Annual Reviews, Inc., 1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - ASILOMAR, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Athena Project, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Augterm Protocol, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - BI/MDC, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Bootstrap Community, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Bannon, Liam, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - British Constabulary, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - CALS, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - C3 OHS Project, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - CMU, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - CSCW, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Center for Coordination of Sciences, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Centrum, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Collaborative Technology, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Computer Aided Thought, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Concurrent Engineering, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      - Critique- Panko, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - Davis Presentation, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - Dexter, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Dialog, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      - Equipment Inventory, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Expenses, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - EXT-RINS, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Faculty Dialog, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Forget Batman, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      - Frame Maker, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 37)
      - Future of Publishing Panel, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - GBS Talk, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 39)
      - Genco, Steve, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Grycz, Chet, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      - Groupware Workshop, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - Hyperdocuments, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Hammer Forum, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - Handbook Project, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - Hart, Paul, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Harvard, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 47)
      - Haarind, Robert, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 48)
      - Hill, David H., 1989 (Box 27, Folder 49)
      - Inter OP '89, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 50)
      - ISDP Workshop, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - JDRS, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 52)
      - Jump Link, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Alpha Files S-Z 1990
      - Steelcase, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Stroll, Dave, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Sun Microsystems, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Seminars 3, 4, & 5 (SEM-3; SEM-4; SEM-5), 1990 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - SHM, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Schael, Thomas, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - SHARE, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Stakeholder Meetings, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - SU, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - TD, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Talks, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Taylor, David, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Thank You Mitch (Kapur), 1990 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Today, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - U Berlin, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - U Karlsruhe, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - U Strathclyde, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Varian Talk, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Veltrop, Bill, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - White Paper, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - W TD, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - WBSI, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - WGBH, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - White, Ellston, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Xanadu, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1991
      - ARC-Journal (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Calendar, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - ABC, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - ACM, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - AF GRoup Support, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Autodesc, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - BForum, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - BI Initiative, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Bootstrap, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Background & Framework, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Berg, Kenneth, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Bloomquist, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Brazil, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Brown, John Seely, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Boostrap Initiative, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - CTC, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - CTS, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Collaboration in Social Architecture, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Colorado Alliance, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Consortium By-Laws, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Coors, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Cutaia, Al, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - DARPA, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Foils, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - France Telecom, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - GCA, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - GBN, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - Grist, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - HP, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - HPCI, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - Hughes, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Hypertext/Hypermedia, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - Inc., 1991 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - Indiana U, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - Interface Group, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - Interap '91, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - Jet Propulsion Lab, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 37)
      - Johnson-Lenz, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - Judson, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - Kaipa, Prasad, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 40)
      - Keyset, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 41)
      - Litto, Frederic M., 1991 (Box 49, Folder 42)
      - Logitech, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 43)
      - MCC, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 44)
      - McGroddy, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 45)
      - Motorola, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 46)
      - NASA, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 47)
      - NRC, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 48)
      - NSF, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 49)
      - OMG Info, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 50)
      - P4 Video, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 51)
      - Pac Bell, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 52)
      - Phone List, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 53)
      - Pooch, Udo, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 54)
      - Price Waterhouse, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 55)
      - Rothermel, John, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 56)
      - SU SHARE, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 57)
      - Seybold, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 58)
      - SITN, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 59)
      - Slides, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 60)
      - Steelcase, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 61)
      - SUN, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 62)
      - To Digest, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 63)
      - Teams, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 64)
      - Touchstone, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 65)
      - UC San Diego, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 66)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1992
      - Calendar, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 69)
      - Annenberg School, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 70)
      - Autmun School, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 71)
      - Boyle, Tim, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 72)
      - Computer World, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 73)
      - Connell, William, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 74)
      - Doubleday, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 75)
      - Electricite de France, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 76)
      - ESI, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 77)
      - ESL, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 78)
      - Eurisco, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 79)
      - Fortune, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 80)
      - Finland, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 81)
      - Groupware '92, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 82)
      - Harris, David, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - IBM, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Interop '92, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Kahn, Bob, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Klarquist, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Koegel, John, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Kohira, Naoniri, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Laky, Les, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Los Alamos, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Lotus, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Marshall, David, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Mork, Dagfish, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Mulconrey, Brian, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - NeoConcepts, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Neurope Lab, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - NIST, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Norway, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - RINS, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Seybold, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Silicon Valley Project, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Silicon Road, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - SRI, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Sun Forum, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Swedish Multimedia Conference, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Syversten, Tor, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - South Bay OD Network, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Stackhouse, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Switzerland, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Tengelsen, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - University de Sao Paolo, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - ARC (Augmentation Research Center), 1972-1986
    - ARC Files, 1972-1986
      - Rose "Information Sharing...", 1978 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Andrews "Line Processor..." (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Hardy "Microprocessor Technology..." (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - NLS (Box 21, Folder 37)
      - Augment Applications & Features, 1977-1986 (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - 1977-1986 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Word Processing, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Office Automation, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 40)
      - Uniform, Consistent, Extensible, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 41)
      - Experimental Development of a Small Computer, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 42)
      - Workstation Equipment, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 43)
      - DEX User Guides, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 44)
      - Graphics User Guide, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 45)
      - RADC Proposal Appendices, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 46)
      - Command Meta Language, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 47)
      - Seybold Report, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 48)
      - Augment, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 49)
      - Seillac II, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 50)
      - Mail Overview, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 51)
      - Misc. Masters (Box 21, Folder 52)
      - Misc. SRI-ARC Publications (Box 21, Folder 53)
      - Misc. SRI-ARC Publications (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals, 1974-1975
      - ARC Journals 25248-25337, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - ARC Journals 25619-25730, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - ARC Journals 25731-25875, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - ARC Journals 25599-26137, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - ARC Journals 26291-26390, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - ARC Journals 34197-34272, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - ARC Journals 33407-33479, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - ARC Journals 28005-28062, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - ARC Journals 28063-28155, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - ARC Journals 28371-28471, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - ARC Journals 27700-27756, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - ARC Journals 27251-27330, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - ARC Journals 26872-26988, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - ARC Journals 26673-26762, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - ARC Journals 26487-26563, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - ARC Journals 28539-28614, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - ARC Journals 29130-29185, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - ARC Journals 28700-28757, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - ARC Journals 21889-22232, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - ARC-Tymshare Files, 1975-1986
      - Diablo Manual (Box 37, Folder 64)
      - ACM History of the Personal Workstation, 1/9-10/1986 (Box 37, Folder 65)
      - Tymshare/Tymnet (Box 37, Folder 66)
      - Presentation Notes, 1980-1982 (Box 37, Folder 67)
      - Correspondence, Memoranda (Box 37, Folder 68)
      - Misc. Reports, DCE & Others (Box 37, Folder 69)
      - ARC Format Library, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - RADC Paperless Lab Report, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Misc. ARC People, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Misc. Brochures, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Binders by Year, 1958-1987
    - Binders, 1958-1963
      - Memos on Magnetic Techniques, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Classified UDOC Lists, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Course on IPL-V & Rand, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Orthagonal Magentic Networks, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Upton "Design for Thinking...", 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - DCE Notes #2, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - References, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - ARC Record 1, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - SRI Economics Division, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Binders, 1965-1968
      - FL, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - DCE Notes X5024-X5032, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - DCE Notes X5033-X5038, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - System Design Software, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Bootstrap Community Planning, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - FLTS Informal Collection, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - DCE Chronological File, 8/1967-11/1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Study for the Development of Human Intellect..., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Movie Scenarios, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - DCE Notes X5039-X5043, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - EWS Papers, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Archive Records, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Binders, 1971-1973
      - XTable Subsys, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 59)
      - Tables, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 60)
      - Trace User Guide, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 61)
      - Org Diag Study, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 62)
      - ARPA/NOSC, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 63)
      - NLS, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 64)
      - Keyboard Mouse Manual, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 65)
      - Line Processor Protocol, 1973-1979 (Box 42, Folder 66)
      - Transparencies, 1973-1979 (Box 42, Folder 67)
      - Reference Notes for Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - DEX, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Plans RWW, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - ARC Baseline, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - DPCS, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Online Teaching of TNLS, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Hypertext Experiment, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - ARPANET News, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - TNLS User Guide, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Binders, 1972-1973
      - DCE Old Worknotes Cleanup, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Plan Notes, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Boostrap Prop Notes, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - DCE Old Notes, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Modular Program System, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - DEX II, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - IPT Contractor Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - WITC, TOWT, KWAC, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - Plan Memos, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - Community Notes, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Binders, 1973-1975
      - DNLS User Guide, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Kirk Kelley Future Plans, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - JCN Planning, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Applications, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - ARC Journal Indices, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - NCC Paper Drafts, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - M Mail Standards, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - DDPCS, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - MDK: NIC (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - XDOC Indices, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - File Records, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Binders, 1974-1975
      - ARC NSW, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - ISI IA Project, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - RWW Planning, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Network Information Center Report, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Programming, Current, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - STC, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - SAFE, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - CONTACT Data, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Binders, 1975-1977
      - Marketing, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - DDPCS, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - ARPA Contractor's Meeting, 3/12-14/1975 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Procedure Call Protocol, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Chase Manhattan Text Processing System Proposal, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - L-10 Design & Application Docs, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - L-10 Programmer's Reference, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - 10X & DEC-20 User Guides, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - AFDSC Documentation Support, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - ARC Computer-Aided Manufacturing, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Binders, 1977-1986
      - Kirk Kelley Senior Thesis, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - ISIS, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Waterloo Script Manual, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - NLS Progref Guides, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - NLS User Guide, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - ARC-SRI Proposal, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - ARC, Inc., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - ARC, Inc. Business Plan Proposal, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Binders
      - Venture Notes, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - AKW Sub-Sys References, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - NLS Programming Reference Guide, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - LIO Programming Documentation, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - ARC References, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Federal Information Processing Standards, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Bootstrap NIO (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - GNOSIS & SCRIPT Conversion, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - UNIX Programmer's Manual, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - HP Plotter Manual, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - XN-10 Specs, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - User Notes, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Binders, 1979-1981
      - File Records, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - XDOC Catalog, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Basic References A-B, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - IAP Notes, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - System Extensions, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - SU COST, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - XD 48867, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - TOPS-20 CMNDS Ref, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - IRD/PRC, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Binders, 1981-1982
      - E Needs & Possibilities, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - EREF, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - RREF, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - XDOC Entries, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - EW, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Ch. SU, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Journal DSS, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - LIO Sources, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Binders
      - PC Programming, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - R-T Exps, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - RTSS, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - XWS & Voter, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - P Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Center, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Application Handbook 1, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Presentation Preparation, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Augment References Misc. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - TOPS-20 User Utilities, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Phone List, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Binders
      - Stanford Conference on Visual Display Terminals, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - SETS, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - RT-CMS, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - SWS & Dev., 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - User Friendly, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Augment Handout, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Mail, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - X Cleanout, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Mail User Guide Draft, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - McDonnell Douglas RPROC Facility, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Mitchell "Production Through Computers", 1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Bootstrap, 1978-1981
    - Bootstrap, 1978-1990
      - Seybold Report - Tymshare Article, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Bootstrap Seminar #1, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Bootstrap Seminar #2, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Bootstrap Seminar #3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Bootstrap Seminar 2 & 5 Binders, CSCW, DECUS, Hyptertext '87, Dictionary, DEC Tapes/STL, Etc., 1982-1990
      - CSCW Conference, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - DECUS Conference, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - EMACS, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - TENEX, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - DEC Tapes in STL, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Hypertext '87, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Bootstrap Seminar #5, 6/19-21/1990 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Bootstrap Seminar #2, 10/24-26/1989 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Bootstrap Project/Stanford University, 1990
      - Financials, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Business Plan, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Sponsors, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Stakeholders, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Status Reports, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Update Letter, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Contacts/Charter Committee, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Clinet Service Meetings (with 5 audiocassettes), 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Services Business Meeting, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Clients (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - MDC Correspondence, 1982-1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Consultants (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Invoices (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - SU Augment License (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Bootstrap, 1990-1991
      - Bootstrap Seminar #5 Transcripts, Audiocassettes, Disks, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Engelbart Notes, 1960-1988
    - DCE Notes Binders, 1960-1965
      - A Project Notes #1, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - A Project Papers, 1960-1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Microdoc, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - DCE Areas of Interest, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - OSR Final Scratch, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Display, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Discs, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - OSR 12 Notes, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - AHI Programming Notes, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - DCE Notes X5000-X5005, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - DCE Notes X5006-X5012, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - DCE Notes X5013-X5023, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - DCE Notes Binders, 1962-1967
      - OSR, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - ARC Record 2, 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - DCE Notes #3, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - ARC Handbook Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - DCE Notes #1, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Systems NP, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - ARC Record 3, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - EE 303, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - DCE Note Binders, 1966-1971
      - NL, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 80)
      - GB 1, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 81)
      - MOL/ARPAS/DDT/QED, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Control Metalanguage, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - NLS, 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - ARC 4 Record, 1967-1969 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - User Group NP, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - ARC Baseline Plans, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - User P&T, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - ARC/IPT Thinkpiece, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Tree Meta in T-M, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - ARC/IPT Proposal, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - DCE Notes Binders, 1969-1971
      - Evans "Man/Computer Augmentation", 1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - USR P&T, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - DCE Notebooks, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - TODAS, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Relevancy, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - ARC Disc Contributors, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Intellectual Implications, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 10)